Welcome to my YouTube channel Guys Hrithik
Technical Support.  In this video we will
tell you how you can get health insurance in Bajaj Finance.
In this video, we will tell you how to get health insurance.  So first of all guys, the
link we have given you in the description is of
Bajaj Finance.  If you
create your account using that link, you will
get referral reward up to ₹5,000.
Ok?  We opened the application.  Then it will
show you this type of interface.
After coming here, you will see that on the home page
you get the option of insurance.  Ok
?  After clicking on Insurance, the
second option is your health
insurance.  You have many companies in health insurance also.
I click on Explore Plan.  So there are many
like you can see Aitya Birla
Group Active Health Plan here.
You can see the premium
of Rs 8182 and you can see the coverage here
Bajaj
Reliance Health Insurance ok there are many
here so as I thought that friend let's
take Bajaj only so let's click on Get Quiet.
And simply you have to enter your
name and your pin code and it will appear in the application.
We will click on Get Quiet.  Ok
?  Now see, you are getting offers here.
Family Health Care Gold wala
and whatever your coverage is up to ₹1 lakh up to ₹3 lakh,
for example I want coverage
up to ₹3 lakh whose premium will be ₹13,000,
so I click on Buy Now.
Stay tuned for our call.  Your journey will be
guided by our experts.  Thank you for
showing your interest.
Ok?  So now we will get a call from their side.  Then he should
guide us as to
what all setup we will have to do.  And he will also
guide you as to what will be the best plan for you.
Ok?  So this is how you will
take health insurance on Bajaj Finance.
So, see you in the next video.